Translated by Releska
The sky of the starry sky
The sky of the sky is so beautiful
It's a day when we're together
I will give you a chance
I will always be with you
Of course, I will always be with you
Yes, yes, yes, yes
With the presence of always being by my side
If I were to be happy with you, I would be happy
The time when the light and the sound of the wind
The sound of the wind is connected
You and you, you and you
If you love me, if you love me
I'll be able to hold you in my arms
I can't believe it!
If you experiment with the machine, it's going to be amazing!
We did a lot of work in this world!
I don't even know where this is going to be.
I don't even know where this is going to be going to be.
But it's not the beginning.
The family of adults is getting closer and closer together.
I had fun with this world together!
A big canvas!
It's amazing!
It's becoming more and more beautiful!
If you don't eat anything, what will you do?
You're going to be born soon, aren't you?
I think it's going to be a good time to be able to do something.
It's time to go!
Let's go!
Welcome back!
Did you get a new toy?
Yes, I heard a new toy.
It looks delicious!
I don't think that's right.
Yo-chan!
You're back?
Did you get a new toy?
Do you want to be with me again tomorrow?
Okay! I'll do it right away!
I couldn't do it because I was at the shop.
That's right.
I can do whatever I want to do in this island.
I'm going to play!
Let's go!
Good!
I want to eat it all day and sleep.
It's too late.
I don't think it's going to be a good time to do something.
It's like I was at the shop.
I thought there was something I was going to use.
That's not good.
I can't do anything without it.
Yay!
I'm going to play today too!
It's the same as usual!
I'm going to play!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm going to the shop!
I'm going to eat it all day.
I feel like I'm going to eat it all day.
Hey, Yano!
Are you worried about me?
I'm not!
I'm going to eat it all day!
I'm going to eat it all day.
Hey!
I'm going to eat it all day!
I'm not going to sleep.
I don't know how to play.
Hey!
I can play with the rules.
Is that also the right answer?
It's not good to have a meeting with the head.
That's right.
What are you thinking about?
Hey, Muka-muka!
You're always in there.
I'm going to play soccer!
No!
I'm going to eat it all day!
But the game is the best.
The game is good, isn't it?
That's why I'm in a lot of trouble.
Hmm?
I have a lot of talent in that.
I know that.
If you say that,
If you're interested in me,
Isn't it good?
I teach you various things like movies, movies, movies, and movies.
Hmm?
Are you interested in me?
No, I'm not.
If you're hungry, you're really hungry?
Hmm?
Muka-muka is different.
Is it good?
Here and here.
Which one is better?
Give it to me.
Hmm.
What should I do?
I don't understand such simple things.
No way.
When you teach children something,
You don't have to do it on purpose.
I don't know what to do.
I don't even know how to do it.
Mom taught me to study in Uiba.
Navatobi.
I won't lose anyone with Natobi and Kuri.
Look at this.
It's the same as Muka-muka.
Muka-muka knows.
There are many of these.
It's true.
Muka-muka, which one is better?
It's not for food.
Hmm.
I stopped by the umbrella.
Then, if you study music,
You won't be able to play Uiba's flute.
Muka-muka, how's it?
Are you studying?
No way.
I didn't think Uiba would study so much.
Muka-muka.
It's hard for you, but do your best.
I did it.
Muka-muka, this.
I used this when I was little.
It's nostalgic.
Now, let's play.
Look.
I'll do it like this.
Muka-muka.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Muka-muka.
Stop it.
Muka-muka has something.
Muka-muka.
You're right.
I'm sure you have something to do.
I believe in you.
Muka-muka.
What's going on?
You're right.
I'm sure you have something to do.
What's going on?
Maybe I'm the one who's wrong.
What?
You're right.
You're wrong.
I'm wrong.
I was just studying.
I think it's because someone who used that.
Someone who used that.
It's not like that.
Why can't I do something like that?
We don't have that much time.
That's right.
Lanka-san is a lot of schedule.
What schedule is there in this place?
What did you do?
Look.
Lanka, did you forget about that?
I was going to wash your hair with that hair.
Oh, that's right.
I was wearing a hat with a long back.
I don't know.
I don't know how to make it look beautiful.
Who is that?
Did you paint that?
It's a lot of money, isn't it?
Or do you paint it?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I was going to tell you.
That's right.
I can't understand that.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Yuu, everyone.
Good morning.
Did you see that?
I think this is it.
How do I do it?
I'm very curious.
Everyone.
Are you all here today?
Yes.
I'm very curious.
What are you doing?
I'm going to go to the classroom.
I was born as a father.
I'm very curious.
I can't tell you.
Everyone is beautiful.
I'm very curious.
Do you know how to be a father?
Do you know who you are?
I don't know.
Do you know how to be a father?
I mean, this is not what I've heard from you.
If you do it, you'll be surprised.
Yes.
Let's go.
Today, I'm going to party with you!
Ah, my head is shaking.
Who is this time?
What is this?
No, no, no!
You're doing the best!
You're not laughing, are you?
That's right!
If you win, everyone will be happy!
I...
Why?
Why did you do it, Muka-chan?
You won't be able to help me, right?
Muka, Muka, Muka, Muka, Muka is so bad.
Muka, Muka...
What do you mean?
Muka, Muka, Muka?
Yeah, Muka, Muka, Muka, Muka...
Muka, Muka, Muka, Muka...
Really?
Yo-chan, don't play with me.
You're not going to play with me?
You're not going to play with me right now, are you?
I'm not going to play with you, everyone.
You're not going to play with me, are you?
It's better to play with me than you.
I think you're going to play with me right now.
What do you mean?
I wanted to play with you.
You want to play with me?
Yeah, I want to play with you, too.
I don't want to play with you.
Muka...
Muka, don't play with your children.
Yeah, that's right.
If you cheer, I'm fine.
Muka...
You don't want to play with me anymore, are you Muka?
Muka, Muka, Muka, Muka, Muka, you're going to play with me right now.
I see.
So you can't play with me right now, are you?
Let's take a picture.
Let's do it like this.
Oh, it's a big one.
It's amazing.
It's a big one.
Oh, it's a big one.
It's a child.
That's right.
It's a big one.
It's a child.
Let's do it like this.
It's good.
It's good, I think.
Did you want to do it?
I think you like it.
We were very impressed.
It's a sketch.
It's fun to play with a pen.
It's a new model.
If you become a model,
It's not easy.
Everyone, let's do it.
It's not easy to play with a sketchbook.
Don't forget it.
It's not easy.
What's that angle?
I thought it was a photo pen.
It's good, isn't it?
What should I draw?
Oh, that's good.
Beautiful water.
It's a sketchbook.
It's good.
I think it's a little different from a child.
It's good, isn't it?
It looks like it's a big one.
Actually, I was really interested in drawing a drawing shop.
Let's do it together.
It's a lot of work.
My game is over.
I didn't draw anything yet.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, isn't it?
Wait, I'm sorry.
I might have drawn a lot earlier.
It's a big one.
What?
I see.
It's a drawing shop.
I don't think it's a drawing shop.
Okay.
Let's draw a drawing shop and go to a wide place.
Even if it's a drawing shop, no one can be attracted to it.
I don't know if you draw it often.
What?
A wide place, a small world.
I don't know why.
I've never seen anything since I was young.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I'm going to take this one.
Dad, I'll draw it.
I'm going to draw this one.
It's a big one.
I'll draw it.
I got it.
I'm glad I didn't get too far.
Is it going to fall down?
It's not easy.
TAAA!
It's going to fall down like this!
It's not going to fall down like this!
Everyone!
I showed you a good thing.
Huh?
It's going to fall down using this.
Yahoo!
It's going to fall down like this!
NONONO!
Hey!
Get out of here!
Right now!
Hey, yuna, go!
Hey, shall we go?
Yes, ok.
Let's go!
Why don't we?
What's going on?
Don't worry about it.
It's been a long time since I've come here.
Let's take a big picture together.
It's hard to come back with such a variety of things.
I'm going to have a lot of fun.
Hey, Uiba.
Yeah.
Hey!
Is something fun going on?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to make me laugh?
I don't know since I'm a little girl.
Hey!
I'm a little girl.
I'm a little girl too.
Hey!
What are you doing?
There it is!
Ah!
current situation!
It's been a while since I've been here, though, Goku.
Goku!
Is it here?
If you don't want to, you'll have to run away from the cave!
Wow! Who wrote that?
Maybe the people of Oumkashi might have written it.
I wonder if the people lived here.
I see.
Kyoryunaka-san is back with a witcher.
Anyway, it's time for you to reveal your face.
Huh? It's time to do it!
It's time to reveal your face!
Oh, I got it.
It's time to reveal your face.
Huh?
It's a dream!
It's a real dream!
It's time to reveal your face.
Hey!
I saw it for the first time in a long time.
Wow, this is a huge gift.
It's a huge gift!
Oh, that's good!
Yuuka-muka, you and I love each other.
Is that so?
Let's go to the morning
There's always a song
Let's sing the song
There's a voice here
There's no way
We are
What is it?
It's the time
If I could
The seed of the old signs
The seed is
hard
Come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come out
Let's go, let's go, let's go, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Let's go to the morning
There is always a song
I want it!
Let's sing the song together!
I'm so interested in your favorite school!
I don't think we're gonna get used to this,
but where are our schoolers gonna go?
Don't worry, Koji Koji-san is doing his best!
Next time, Gunka Paradais, Gunka Osura Kyosutsu!
Looking forward to it!